

DAVID JAHNS

FRONT END / UX DEVELOPER

Phone (630) 267 2008

Email imdavidjahns@gmail.com

Website www.davidjahns.com

101 Gatewood Ave

Nashville, TN 37207

Get to know me at:









Education

May 2015

B.S. - Web Development and Programming

Belmont University Nashville, TN

2012 - Present

Online Learning

Online Tutorials

Treehouse.com, Codecademy.com, Lynda.com

I am always using my free time to keep up and learn new skills in web and even some iOS development

Employment

May 2014 - Present

Front End / UX Intern

HCA Healthcare - IT&S

Interning with the Creative Strategy and Experience team doing front end development and prototyping for a variety of healthcare related websites and web apps.

May 2013 - August 2014

Mobile Technician

APPLE

Troubleshooting and repairing iOS devices on the software, firmware, and hardware levels in a high volume appointment-based setting. Facilitating one-on-one and group trainings: teaching the ins and outs of OS X and iOS devices and software.

June 2012 - May 2013

Specialist

APPLE

Finding the right technology solution for a customer based on their needs. Facilitated/taught group workshops for Mac and iOS.

About Me

Address

Name: David Jahns
DOB: 10/18/1988
Location: East Nashville
Exprience: 2+ Years coding
Availability: Fulltime

Likes: Music, Shows, Craft Beer, Nature, etc.

My Objective

I have a passion for the user experience. I believe that the user comes first in every aspect of a product including design, performance, and accessibility.

I am seeking a Front End or Junior Front End Developer position with a company that strives to make beautiful, easy to use products, and has a great team culture.

Professional Skill

HTML

CSS

Javascript

OOP

Git

Photoshop

Illustrator

Knowledgable / comfortable using

jQuery, AJAX, PHP, Java, Bootstrap, Yeoman, Bower, Grunt, Jekyll, Tumblr themes, CodeKit, GitHub, Basecamp, Slack, Trello, etc.

Personal fan of / interested in

Material Design, Atomic Design, JS frameworks like Ember and Angular, D3.js, Swift / iOS Development.